const previousLetter = [
    { question: 'ą', answers: ['a'] },
    { question: 'b', answers: ['ą'] },
    { question: 'c', answers: ['b'] },
    { question: 'ć', answers: ['c'] },
    { question: 'd', answers: ['ć'] },
    { question: 'e', answers: ['d'] },
    { question: 'ę', answers: ['e'] },
    { question: 'f', answers: ['ę'] },
    { question: 'g', answers: ['f'] },
    { question: 'h', answers: ['g'] },
    { question: 'i', answers: ['h'] },
    { question: 'j', answers: ['i'] },
    { question: 'k', answers: ['j'] },
    { question: 'l', answers: ['k'] },
    { question: 'ł', answers: ['l'] },
    { question: 'm', answers: ['ł'] },
    { question: 'n', answers: ['m'] },
    { question: 'ń', answers: ['n'] },
    { question: 'o', answers: ['ń'] },
    { question: 'ó', answers: ['o'] },
    { question: 'p', answers: ['ó'] },
    { question: 'r', answers: ['p'] },
    { question: 's', answers: ['r'] },
    { question: 'ś', answers: ['s'] },
    { question: 't', answers: ['ś'] },
    { question: 'u', answers: ['t'] },
    { question: 'w', answers: ['u'] },
    { question: 'y', answers: ['w'] },
    { question: 'z', answers: ['y'] },
    { question: 'ź', answers: ['z'] },
    { question: 'ż', answers: ['ź'] },
];

export default previousLetter;
